{
    "response_code": 0,
    "results": [
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Solve : $\n\\int_0^{\\frac{\\pi}{2}} \\sin ^3 \\theta \\cos \\theta d \\theta\n$",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In the expansion of $ \\left(x+\\sqrt{x^2-1} \\right)^6 + \\left(x-\\sqrt{x^2-1}\\right)^6$. Find the number of terms",
        "correct_answer": "Nitrogen",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Oxygen",
          "Hydrogen",
          "Neon"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "If $(1+x)^n=C_0+C_1 x+C_2 x^2+\\ldots  C_n x^n$. Prove that $C_0C_1+C_1C_2+.....C_{n-1}C_n=\\frac{2n!}{(n-1)!(n+1)!}$",
        "correct_answer": "Candela",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Willow",
          "Blanche",
          "Spark"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "If $\\int_{-\\frac1{\\sqrt{3}}}^{\\frac1{\\sqrt{3}}} \\frac{x^4}{1-x^4} \\cos ^{-1} \\frac{2 x}{1+x^2} d x=-\\frac{\\pi}{\\sqrt{3}}-\\frac{\\pi}{4} \\log \\left(\\frac{\\sqrt{3}-1}{\\sqrt{3}+1}\\right)+k$, then $k=?$",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the expansion of $ \\left(\\frac{4x}{5}-\\frac{5}{2x}\\right)^9\\\\$\nFind the 7th term.",
        "correct_answer": "Diane",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Sakura",
          "Ayano",
          "Sheska"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the expansion of $ \\left(ax^2+\\frac{1}{bx}\\right)^{11}$, find the coefficient of $x^7$.",
        "correct_answer": "Vincent Vega",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Jules Winnfield",
          "Jimmie Dimmick",
          "Butch Coolidge"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Books",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Solve: $\\int_{-4}^3|x^2 -4| d x$",
        "correct_answer": "Holden Caulfield",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Fletcher Christian",
          "Jay Gatsby",
          "Randall Flagg"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Solve : $\n\\int_0^{\\frac{\\pi}{2}} \\sin ^3 \\theta \\cos \\theta d \\theta\n$",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Science & Nature",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "In the expansion of $ \\left(x+\\sqrt{x^2-1} \\right)^6 + \\left(x-\\sqrt{x^2-1}\\right)^6$. Find the number of terms",
        "correct_answer": "Nitrogen",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Oxygen",
          "Hydrogen",
          "Neon"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "If $(1+x)^n=C_0+C_1 x+C_2 x^2+\\ldots  C_n x^n$. Prove that $C_0C_1+C_1C_2+.....C_{n-1}C_n=\\frac{2n!}{(n-1)!(n+1)!}$",
        "correct_answer": "Candela",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Willow",
          "Blanche",
          "Spark"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "hard",
        "question": "If $\\int_{-\\frac1{\\sqrt{3}}}^{\\frac1{\\sqrt{3}}} \\frac{x^4}{1-x^4} \\cos ^{-1} \\frac{2 x}{1+x^2} d x=-\\frac{\\pi}{\\sqrt{3}}-\\frac{\\pi}{4} \\log \\left(\\frac{\\sqrt{3}-1}{\\sqrt{3}+1}\\right)+k$, then $k=?$",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the expansion of $ \\left(\\frac{4x}{5}-\\frac{5}{2x}\\right)^9\\\\$\nFind the 7th term.",
        "correct_answer": "Diane",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Sakura",
          "Ayano",
          "Sheska"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Film",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "In the expansion of $ \\left(ax^2+\\frac{1}{bx}\\right)^{11}$, find the coefficient of $x^7$.",
        "correct_answer": "Vincent Vega",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Jules Winnfield",
          "Jimmie Dimmick",
          "Butch Coolidge"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "Entertainment: Books",
        "type": "multiple",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "question": "Solve: $\\int_{-4}^3|x^2 -4| d x$",
        "correct_answer": "Holden Caulfield",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "Fletcher Christian",
          "Jay Gatsby",
          "Randall Flagg"
        ]
      },
      {
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "medium",
        "question": "Solve : $\n\\int_0^{\\frac{\\pi}{2}} \\sin ^3 \\theta \\cos \\theta d \\theta\n$",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
          "True"
        ]
      }
    ]
  }